<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>100% Wool on Hugo Curate</title>
    <link>/categories/100-wool/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 100% Wool on Hugo Curate</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/100-wool/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Funnel Neck Boxy Fit Boiled Wool Sweater</title>
      <link>/projects/eileen-fisher-boiled-wool/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/eileen-fisher-boiled-wool/</guid>
      <description>A boiled wool sweater the color of manzanita half price at Nordstrom Rack. My Universe knows me well!
This sweater is SO cozy yet oddly lightweight. The fabric, described as &amp;ldquo;jersey&amp;rdquo; by the brand, is 100% wool but moves and drapes like cotton. It&amp;rsquo;s wonderful. It&amp;rsquo;s so soft, it feels like you have nothing on, which is my preference, except that I live in the foothills with thirty degree rain so even indoors it&amp;rsquo;s not really an option.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oversized One-of-a-kind Mohair Wool Sweater</title>
      <link>/projects/flashbacks-encinitas-giant-mohair/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/flashbacks-encinitas-giant-mohair/</guid>
      <description>I found this gem at Flashbacks in Encinitas years and years ago. Pretty sure I was living at the cabin in Old Town at the time so it had to be somewhere around 2012 or 13. You know what? Everyone still loves this sweater. I don&amp;rsquo;t even wear it if I&amp;rsquo;m not in the mood to be complimented.
I wish I knew who made this sweater. It&amp;rsquo;s clearly handmade and the maker has amazing taste.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunchild Blue Wool Cardigan</title>
      <link>/projects/sunchild-blue-wool-cardigan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/sunchild-blue-wool-cardigan/</guid>
      <description>The color of deep ocean swimming, this sweater is a vibrant mix of royal blue and teal with cornflower blue buttons. In a sea of earth tones, this sweater doesn&amp;rsquo;t mind choosing a saturated spot on the color wheel. Honestly, don&amp;rsquo;t we all have enough beige sweaters at this point?
This is another vintage store find handmade by an unsung hero. And like my gigantic mohair sweater, I get complimented on it every time I wear it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
