<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Aubrey Coon on Hugo Curate</title>
    <link>/authors/aubrey-coon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Aubrey Coon on Hugo Curate</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/authors/aubrey-coon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Find The Best Sweaters on YOOX</title>
      <link>/blog/2024/01/how-to-find-the-best-sweaters-on-yoox/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2024/01/how-to-find-the-best-sweaters-on-yoox/</guid>
      <description>I discovered YOOX browsing for sweaters Noel Fielding has worn on the Great British Baking Show and wow is it a lot of fun. It&amp;rsquo;s not a new site by a long shot but it&amp;rsquo;s new to me! Part of the YOOX Net-A-Porte group since their 2015 merger, YOOX is a gathering place for past season clothes and also serves as a clearance site for items that haven&amp;rsquo;t sold at retail price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Worth it? Why Choose Natural Fiber Sweaters Over Synthetic</title>
      <link>/blog/2024/01/worth-it-why-choose-natural-fiber-sweaters-over-synthetic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2024/01/worth-it-why-choose-natural-fiber-sweaters-over-synthetic/</guid>
      <description>What we wear on our bodies has an impact on us. As we continue to evolve, raise our awareness and heighten our senses, many of us are realizing that the products and clothing we choose to surround ourselves with has a huge impact, not only on our home planet but on our bodies and our minds.
When I wear a sweater or any piece of clothing that is made of wool, or cotton or any other natural fiber, my skin knows it and my nervous system responds with a feeling of safety and ease.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Does Host of the Great British Baking Show, Noel Fielding, Get His Amazing Sweaters??</title>
      <link>/blog/2024/01/where-does-host-of-the-great-british-baking-show-noel-fielding-get-his-amazing-sweaters/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2024/01/where-does-host-of-the-great-british-baking-show-noel-fielding-get-his-amazing-sweaters/</guid>
      <description>Every time I watch the Great British Baking Show I want to know where the heck Noel Fielding gets his amazing clothes, especially his sweaters. And I just realized that everyone else wants to know too! There&amp;rsquo;s an entire instagram account devoted to his wardrobe. I was delighted to find some gorgeous merino in the mix. Here are some of the brands making Noel&amp;rsquo;s cool sweaters.
Wah Wah This Australian brand is truly niche – turning punk album artwork into wearable art with fine merino wool and unforgettable designs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
